Guide to the Andrew F. Smith Collection of Cookery Ephemera MSS.295
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Cookery Ephemera, 1798-2009
  - Eagle Library Publications; Early American Society, Inc., 1930, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Eagle. The Eagle Cook Book and Household Manual. Eagle Library Number 290. Brooklyn: Eagle Library Publications, 1930.
  - E.C. Harley Company; E.C. Rich, 1910, 1920s (Box 13, Folder 10)
    E. C. Harley Company. The Chef. Dayton, OH: E. C. Harley Company, 1910.
    E. C. Rich. Rich's Tryphosa. New York, NY: E. C. Rich, 1920s.
  - Edward Woollery's Sugar Mill, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Egg-o-See Cereal with E. Brate Rogers; Epoca, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Epoca. Brazil's Matte Tea (brochure). Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
  - Emerson Radio Corporation; Erie Preserving Company, circa 1920s, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Erie Preserving Co. A Book of Heraldry. Buffalo, NY: Erie Preserving Co., undated.
    Emerson Radio Corp. Microwave Cooking. Japan: Emerson Radio Corp., undated.
  - Engman Matthews Range Company; Enterprise Manufacturing Company of Pennsylvania, 1899, 1920s (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Engman Matthews Range Co. Selected Recipes of All Nations. Goshen, IN: Engman Matthews Range Co, circa 1920.
    Enterprise Manufacturing Company of Pa. Patent Hardware Specialties. Philadelphia, PA: Enterprise Manufacturing Company of Pa., 1899.
  - E. R. Durkee & Company--Durkee Famous Foods, Inc., 1875-1934 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Durkee. E. R. Durkee & Co's Practical Cook Book. New York, NY: E. R. Durkee Co., 1875.
    Durkee. Cook Book. With Upward of 250 Useful and Economical Recipes. New York, NY: E. R. Durkee & Co., 1885.
    Durkee. "Durkee's Salad Dressing." New York, NY: E. R. Durkee & Co., 1907.
    Durkee. Durkee Famous Food Recipes; A Century of Progress, Chicago, 1933. New York, NY: Durkee Famous Foods, Inc., 1933.
    Durkee. A Century of Progress, Chicago. Elmhurst, NY: Durkee Famous Foods, Inc., 1934.
  - E. R. Sherburne Company; E. T. Cowdrey Company, circa 1900, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - The Eureka Salt Manufacturing Company, Limited, 1886 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Evangeline Chapter No. 93-- Sweets and Meats and Other Good Things to Eat, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Evaporated Milk Association; Family Brick Products Company, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Evaporated Milk Association. Food Fit for Camping Appetites. Place of publication unknown: Evaporated Milk Association, 1927.
    Family Brick Products Co. Ice Cream Recipes. Los Angeles, CA: Alfred's Pure Ice Cream, undated.
  - Family Circle with Sylvia Schur, 1900, circa 1980s (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Farmers Market: Los Angeles Souvenir; The Farmer's Wife, circa 1900, 1940-1950s (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Felin's Pure Pork Products--Harry Walbaum Meat Market; F.H. Marshall, Commission Merchant, 1881, circa 1970s (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Findley, Reverend William T., 1860 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Fine Groceries Account Book, circa 1900 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Fish and Tuna Research, 1914-1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Shurtleff-Taylor Co. "Ask Your Grocer for" (card). Los Angeles: Shurtleff-Taylor Co., undated.
  - Fisher Flouring Mills Company, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Fisher Flouring Mills Co. The Fairies Cook Book. Tacoma, Seattle and Portland: Fisher Flouring Mills Co., undated.
  - The Fitzgerald Manufacturing Company; Five Roses Kitchen with Pauline Harvey, 1932, circa 1950s (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Fitzgerald Manufacturing. Prize-Winning Recipes from Radio Contests. Star-Rite Magic Maid. Torrington, CT: The Fitzgerald Manufacturing Company, 1932.
  - Fleischmann & Company, 1839-1904 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Fleischmann Co. Choice Recipes: How to Make the Finest Bread and the Most Delicious Cakes, Pastry, Etc. New York, NY: Fleischmann Co., 1893.
    Fleischmann & Co. Selected Recipes. How to Make the Finest Bread and the Most Delicious Rolls By the Use of Compressed Yeast. New York, NY: Fleischmann & Co., undated.
    Fleischmann Company. Choice Recipes How to Make the Finest Bread and the Most Delicious Cakes, Pastry, Etc. New York, NY: The Fleischmann Company, 1902.
  - The Fleishmann Company, 1889-1920 (Box 14, Folder 9-14)
    Fleischmann Co. Fleischmann's Booklet Devoted to the Interests of Good Baking. New York, NY: Fleischmann Co., 1907.
    Fleischmann Company. Excellent Recipes for Baking Raised Breads. Cincinnati, OH: The Fleischmann Company, 1910.
    Fleischmann Company. Delicious Food Made with Cereals & Flour. New York, Cincinnati, San Francisco: The Fleischmann Company, circa 1915.
    Fleischmann Company. Excellent Recipes for Baking Raised Bread; Also Directions for Making Refreshing Summer Drinks. New York, NY: The Fleischmann Company, 1914.
    Fleischmann Company. Excellent Recipes for Baking Raised Bread; Also Directions for Making Refreshing Summer Drinks. New York, NY: The Fleischmann Company, 1915.
    Fleischmann Company. Excellent Recipes for Baking Raised Bread; Also Directions for Making Refreshing Summer Drinks. New York, NY: The Fleischmann Company, 1916.
    Fleischmann Company. Excellent Recipes for Baking Raised Bread; Also Directions for Making Refreshing Summer Drinks. New York, NY: The Fleischmann Company, 1917.
    Fleischmann Company. Neil, Marion Harris. Sixty-five Delicious Dishes Made with Bread. Cincinnati, OH: The Fleischmann Company, 1919.
  - Florida Avocado Administrative Committee; Florida Citrus Exchange, 1931, circa 1980-1990s (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Florida Avocado Administrative Committee. Florida Avocado Recipes. Homestead, FL: Florida Avocado Administrative Committee, undated.
    Florida Citrus Exchange. Frank, M.G. Keeping Well with Oranges and Grapefruit. Tampa: Florida Citrus Exchange, 1931.
  - Francis H. Leggett & Company, 1911 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Leggett. Premier Pure Foods. New York, NY: Francis H. Leggett & Co., 1911.
    Francis H. Leggett & Co. Salads, Suppers, Picnics– A Book of Delicious and Time Saving Dishes Made with Premier Salad Dressing. New York, NY: Francis H. Leggett & Co., undated.
  - Franco-American Food Company, 1900, 1908 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Franco-American Food Company. (card). Place of publication unknown: Franco-American Food Company, undated.
    Franco-American Food Company. Biardot, A. Franco-American Soups and Other Specialties: A Description of Each Variety. Jersey City Heights, NJ: The Franco-American Food Company, 1900.
    Franco-American Food Company. For Invalids For Babies and Children. Jersey City Heights, NJ: Franco-American Food Co., 1908.
  - Frank E. Davis Fish Company, circa 1900 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Frank E. Davis Co. Fish Recipes. Gloucester, MA: Frank E. Davis Co., circa 1900.
  - Frankfort Distilleries, Inc. with Irvin S. Cobb, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Franklin Baker Company; Franklin Mills Company, circa 1900, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Franklin Baker Company. Baker's Coconut Recipes. Philadelphia, PA: The Franklin Baker Company, 1923.
    Franklin Flour Mills. The Best Food for Man Since the Grinding of Grain. Lockport, NY: Franklin Flour Mills, undated.
  - Franklin Peanut Company, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Franklin Sugar Refining Company, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Franklin Sugar Refining Co. The Franklin Sugar Sweetmeat Book. Philadelphia, PA: Franklin Sugar Refining Co., 1923.
  - Frederick C. Mathews Company--Rossell's Ice Cream, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Frederick C. Mathews Company. Some Helps for Ice Cream Dispensers. Second Revised edition. Detroit, MI: Frederick C. Mathews Company, 1919.
  - Fred'k Dutcher Drug Company, circa 1900 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Dutcher Drug Co. Candy Recipes. St. Albans, VT: Fred'k Dutcher Drug Co., undated.
  - Frigidaire Corporation, 1928-1929 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Frigidaire Corporation. Frozen Deserts and Salads Made in Frigidaire. Dayton, OH: Frigidaire Corporation, 1928.
    Frigidaire Corporation. Miller, Verna L. Frigidaire Frozen Delights; Especially Prepared for Apartments with Frigidaire. Dayton, OH: Frigidaire Corporation, 1929.
  - Frito-Lay, Inc., 1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Frito-Lay. The Imagination Cookbook from Doritos Brand Tortilla Chips. Dallas, TX: Frito-Lay, Inc., 1978.
  - Fromm & Sichel, Inc., circa 1950s (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Fromm and Sichel, Inc. Better Cooking and Entertaining with Great American Wines. New York, NY: Fromm and Sichel, Inc., undated.
  - Fruit Dispatch Company, 1923-1926, 1940-1947 (Box 15, Folder 12-13)
    Fruit Dispatch Company. Selected Banana Recipes for Appetizing and Nutritious Dishes Relishes, Vegetables, Salads Desserts. New York, NY: Fruit Dispatch Company, 1923.
    Fruit Dispatch Company. From the Tropics to Your Table Eighty-three Tested Banana Recipes. New York, NY: Fruit Dispatch Company, 1926.
    Fruit Dispatch Company. Bananas Take a Bow in Attractive New Dishes for the Up-to-date Hostess. New York, NY: Fruit Dispatch Company, undated.
    Fruit Dispatch Company. Banana Frozen Desserts. New York, NY: Fruit Dispatch Company, 1940.
    Fruit Dispatch Company. Serve Bananas in "Latest Style". New York, NY: Fruit Dispatch Company, 1940.
    Fruit Dispatch Company. Bananas. How to Serve Them. New York, NY: Fruit Dispatch Company, 1941.
    Fruit Dispatch Company. Banana Salad Bazar. New York, NY: Fruit Dispatch Company, undated.
    Fruit Dispatch Company. Banana Specialities. New York, NY: Fruit Dispatch Company, undated.
    Fruit Dispatch Company. Tempting Banana Recipes. New York, NY: United Fruit Company, 1947.
  - G. W. Martin & Brother, 1884 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Garrett & Company, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Gebhardt Chili Powder Company, 1911-1949 (Box 15, Folder 16-19)
    Gebhardt. Promotions. San Antonio, TX: Gebhardt Chili Powder Company, undated.
    Gebhardt. Mexican Cooking: The Flavor of the 20th Century--that Real Mexican Tang. San Antonio, TX: Gebhardt Chili Powder Company.
    Gebhardt. Mexican Cooking: The Flavor of the 20th Century--that Real Mexican Tang. San Antonio, TX: Gebhardt Chili Powder Company, 1911.
    Gebhardt. Mexican Cookery for American Homes. San Antonio, TX: Gebhardt Chili Powder Company, 1923.
    Gebhardt. Bradley, Alice. Salads Alluring and New. San Antonio, TX: Gebhardt Chili Powder Company, 1926.
    Gebhardt. Mexican Cookery for American Homes. San Antonio, TX: Gebhardt Chili Powder Company, 1932.
    Gebhardt. Mexican Cookery for American Homes. San Antonio, TX: Gebhardt Chili Powder Company, undated.
    Gebhardt. Mexican Cookery for American Homes. San Antonio, TX: Gebhardt Chili Powder Company, 1943.
    Gebhardt. Mexican Cookery for American Homes. San Antonio, TX: Gebhardt Chili Powder Company, 1949.
  - General Baking Company, 1931, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    General Baking Co. The Bond Book of Recipes. Place of publication unknown: General Baking Co., 1935.
    General Baking Co. Bond Bread Cook Book. Place of publication unknown: General Baking Co., 1935.
    General Baking Co. 88 Mealtime Surprises Made with Bond Bread. Place of publication unknown: General Baking Company, 1931.
  - General Electric Company, circa 1960-1980s (Box 15, Folder 21)
    General Electric Company. Recipes for Table Top Cookery. Bridgeport, CT: General Electric Company, undated.
    General Electric Company. Facts about Your New GE Mixer. Place of publication unknown: General Electric Company, undated.
    General Electric Company. 52 Recipes for the General Electric Waffle Iron; One for Every Sunday Evening in the Year. Bridgeport, CT, and Ontario, CA: General Electric Company, undated.
    General Electric Company. Use and Care Book Deluxe Toast-R-Oven. Bridgeport, CT: General Electric, undated.
    General Electric Company. Cajun/Creole Cooking; The Microwave Way. Place of publication unknown: General Electric Company, undated.
  - General Foods Corporation, 1931-1965, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 22, Box 16, Folder 1-3)
    General Foods. Barton, Frances Lee. New Cake Secrets. Evansville, IN: Iglehart Brothers, Inc., General Food Corporation Corp, 1931.
    General Foods. The Calumet Baking Book. New edition. Place of publication unknown: General Foods Corporation, 1931.
    General Foods. Correct Salads for All Occasions. Long Island City, NY: Richard Hellmann, Inc., 1931.
    General Foods. The Calumet Book of Oven Triumphs. Place of publication unknown: General Foods Corporation, 1934.
    General Foods. Salads and Entrées. New York, NY: General Foods Corporations, 1939.
    General Foods Corporation. Barton, Frances Lee, comp. More Fun... in the Kitchen. New York, NY: General Foods Corporation, 1951.
    General Foods. Exciting World of Rice Dishes. White Plains, NY: General Foods Corporation, 1959.
    General Foods. Wake Up to Tang and New Ways to Enjoy It. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
    General Foods. Baker's Chocolate and Coconut Favorites. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
    General Foods. Bright Ideas for the Holidays. Place of publication unknown: Kraft General Foods, 1989.
  - General Foods Corporation--Jell-O Company, Inc., 1925-1937, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
    Jell-O Company. For More than a Quarter of a Century. Le Roy, NY: Jell-O Company, undated.
    Jell-O Co. Through the Menu with Jell-O. Le Roy, NY: Jell-O Co., 1927.
    Jell-O Company. The New Jell-O Book of Surprises; Desserts, Salads. Le Roy, NY: Jell-O Company, 1930.
    Jell-O Company. Jell-O America's Most Famous Dessert. Le Roy, NY: The Jell-O Company, 1926.
    Jell-O. Quick Easy Jell-O Wonder Dishes. Le Roy, NY: The Jell-O Company, 1930.
    General Foods. Try the New Jell-O You Make it Without Boiling Water, 48 New Jell-O Recipes. Le Roy, NY: The Jell-O Company, Inc., Division of General Foods Corporation, 1932.
    Jell-O Co. Jell-O Book of Menus. Le Roy, NY: Jell-O Co., undated.
    Jell-O. What Mrs. Dewey did with the New Jell-O; 48 Fascinating New Recipes. Le Roy, NY: The Jell-O Company, a Division of General Foods Corporation, 1933.
    Jell-O and Dream Whip. Recipes for the Cream of the Cream Pies. Place of publication unknown: Division of General Foods Corporation, undated.
  - General Mills, Inc., 1960-1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    General Mills. Christmas Edition Gold Medal Flour Cook Book. Minneapolis, MN: Washburn Crosby Co., 1904. Reprint. Minneapolis, Minnesota: General Mills, 1970.
    General Mills. "Let's Eat Outdoors" A Cook Book of Recipes and Ideas for Picnics, Barbecues, Patio Parties, Cooking. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
  - General Mills, Inc.--Betty Crocker, 1933-1969 (Box 16, Folder 7-9)
    General Mills. Betty Crocker's 101 Delicious Bisquick Creations As Made and Served by Well-Known Gracious Hostesses; Famous Chefs; Distinguished Epicures and Smart Luminaries of Movieland. Minneapolis, MN: General Mills, Inc., 1933.
    General Mills. Let the Stars Show You How to Take a Trick a Day with Bisquick as Told to Betty Crocker. Minneapolis, MN: General Mills, 1935.
    General Mills. Your Share How to Prepare Appetizing, Healthful Meals with Foods Available Today, Betty Crocker. Minneapolis, MN: General Mills, Inc., 1943.
    General Mills. Your Share How to Prepare Appetizing, Healthful Meals with Foods available Today, Betty Crocker. Minneapolis, MN: General Mills, Inc., 1943.
    General Mills. Betty Crocker's Holiday Heritage. Minneapolis, MN: General Mills, Inc., 1966.
    General Mills. 133 Quicker Ways to Homemade. With Bisquick from Betty Crocker. Minneapolis, MN: General Mills, Inc., 1959.
    General Mills. Betty Crocker's Bisquick Party Book. Minneapolis, MN: General Mills, Inc., 1957.
    General Mills. New! From Gold Medal Candy Cookies, Betty Crocker. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
    Gold Medal Foods, Inc., of General Mills. New Party Cake for All Occasions. Minneapolis, MN: Gold Medal Foods, Inc., of General Mills, 1951.
    Kroger Stores. Advertisement fo Betty Crocker's Milk Chocolate Cake. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
  - General Motors Corporation, 1926, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Delco-Light Co. Frozen Desserts and Salads Made in Frigidaire. Dayton, OH: Delco-Light Company, 1926.
    General Motors. Recipes from Many Lands; Women's International Exposition 1951. Place of publication unknown: General Motors, undated.
  - Genesee Pure Food Company--Jell-O, 1918-1922 (Box 16, Folder 11-12, Box 44, Folder 5)
    Genesee Pure Food Company. New Talks about Jell-O America's Most Famous Dessert. Le Roy, NY: The Genesee Pure Food Company, 1918.
    Genesee Pure Food Company. Jell-O America's Most Famous Dessert. Le Roy, NY: The Genesee Pure Food Company, 1920.
    Genesee Pure Food Company. For Economy Use, Jell-O America's Most Famous Dessert. Le Roy, NY: The Genesee Pure Food Company, 1922.
    Genesee Pure Food Company. Jell-O America's Most Famous Dessert. Le Roy, NY: The Genesee Pure Food Company, undated.
    Genesee Pure Food Company. Jell-O: America's Most Famous Dessert with "Jell-O Ice Cream Powder." Le Roy, NY: The Genesee Pure Food Company. 1916.
  - George H. Cross Company; George M. Clark & Company, 1902, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    American Stove Company. Just a Cook Book for Economical Gas Cooking. Chicago, IL: George M. Clark Division, American Stove Company, 1902.
    Geo. H. Cross. A Few Dainty Dishes Prepared by the Use of St. Johnsbury Crackers. St. Johnsbury, VT: Geo. H. Cross, after 1912.
  - George P. Thomas with Ida Cogswell Bailey Allen; G. F. Heublein & Brother--A1 Sauce, circa 1900, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    G. F. Heublein & Bro. 25 Ways to a Man's Heart by a Housewife Who Knows. Hartford: G. F. Heublein & Bro., undated.
  - The G. H. Hammond Company, circa 1900 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Hammond Co. Cookene. South Omaha, NE and Hammond, IN: The G. H. Hammond Co., undated.
  - Gibbons, Barbara, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Gies & Company, circa 1870s (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Crystal Gelatine. Crystal Gelatine A Pure Gelatine Guaranteed to Make Two Quarts of Jelly. Boston, MA: Crystal Gelatine, undated.
  - Girnau, Frederic H., 1942, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Heileman Brewing Company. 300 New Ways of Making Delicious Sandwiches. Minneapolis, MN: Frederic H. Girnau Creations, 1945.
    Universal F. H. G. Creations. Girnau, Frederic H. Cedric Adams Cook Book on Fish and Sea-Food Cookery. Place of publication unknown: Universal F. G. H. Creations, 1942.
  - Goddard, F. B. with T. E. Carr & Son, 1888 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Middleton, Carman & Co. Goddard, F. B. Marketing: a Reliable Guide to the Purchase of Meats, Poultry, Game, Fish, Vegetables, Fruits. New York, NY: The Tradesman's Publishing Company, 1887.
  - Golden Gate Bridge Compressed Yeast Company; Jenny Wren Company, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Golden Gate Compressed Yeast Co. Home Made Bread. San Francisco, CA: Golden Gate Compressed Yeast Co. undated.
    Jenny Wren Company. Jenny Wren Recipes. Lawrence, KS: Jenny Wren Company, undated.
  - Golden State Ice Cream; Good Housekeeping Magazine, circa 1940s, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Good Luck Food Company, Inc., circa 1940s (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Good Luck. Short Cuts to Delicious Desserts with Good Luck. Rochester, NY: Good Luck Co., Inc., undated.
  - G. P. Gundlach & Company; G. P. Putnam's Sons, circa 1940s, 1881 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Peoples Dairy. Cottage Cheese for the Modern Little Miss Muffet. Place of publication unknown: Peoples Dairy, undated.
  - Grand Lodge of Iowa, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The Grand Union Company, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Grand Union. Recipe Book. New York, NY: Grand Union Company, 1931.
  - Grant, Erdon L., 1901 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - The Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company. Colonel Goodbody's Red Setter Menus. Place of publication unknown: The Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co., undated.
    Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company. Grocery Catalogue 1912. Wheeler Block, Glen Cove, NY: Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company, 1912.
  - Great Western Sugar Cookbooks, circa 1960-1970s (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Great Western Sugar Co. A GW Sugar Taste Treat; Coconut Bars. Denver, CO: Great Western Sugar Co., undated.
    Great Western Sugar Co. A GW Sugar Taste Treat; Lemon Frosted Pecan Bars. Denver, CO: Great Western Sugar Co., undated.
    Great Western Sugar Co. 44 Exciting GW Cookbooks You'll Want Them All. Denver, CO: Great Western Sugar Co., undated.
  - Green, Roberta, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - The Gunnard Company; Grocery Store Products Company, circa 1935, circa 1990s (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Gunnar Company. Ahlquist, Gunnar. Canning and Preserving. Fourteenth edition. Minneapolis, MN: The Gunnar Company, circa 1935, revised 1945.
  - Gwaltney-Bunkley Peanut Company, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Gwaltney-Bunkley Peanut Co. The Land of the Peanut. Smithfield, VA: The Gwaltney-Bunkley Peanut Co., 1904.
  - Gwinnett County Public Library's Meet The Author: Andrew Smith, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - H. A. Johnson Company, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    H. A. Johnson Co. Sixty Years: 1877-1937. New York, NY: H. A. Johnson Co., 1937.
  - Hallet & Davis Piano Company, circa 1850s (Box 17, Folder 18)
    Hallet & Davis Piano Co. A Friend in Need is a Friend Indeed. Boston, MA: Hallet & Davis Piano Co., undated.
  - Hallock Fireless Cooker Company; Hamilton Beach Company, 1907, 1948-1990s (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Hallock Fireless Cooker Company. How to Cook Without Fire; An Interesting Story for the Woman who Cooks. Grand Rapids, MI: Hallock Fireless Cooker Company, undated.
    Hamilton Beach. Hamilton Beach Food Mixer. Racine, WI: Hamilton Beach, 1948.
    Hamilton Beach. Order Direct from Hamilton Beach; Complete Catalog of Cookbooks, Accessories and Replacement Parts. WA, NC: Hamilton Beach, undated.
    Hamilton Beach. Tested Recipes and Instructions for the Hamilton Beach Model B Food Mixer and Attachments. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
  - Hamlin's Wizard Oil Company; Hammond, Inc., circa 1850s, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    Hamlin's Wizard Oil Co. Hamlin's Wizard Oil Co's Cook Book. Chicago, IL: Hamlin's Wizard Oil Co., undated.
  - Harper-Wyman Company, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - The Harvard Dental Parlors, circa 1850s (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Harvard Dental Parlors. The Harvard Cook Book. Bronx, NY: Harvard Dental Parlors, undated.
  - Harvey's Famous Restaurant, circa 1970-1980s (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Harvey's. Romer, Frank. The History of Harvey's [Restaurant]. WA, DC: Harvey's Restaurant, undated.
  - The Hawaiian (Dole) Pineapple Company; Hawaiian Pineapple Company, Limited, 1929, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 6, Box 18, Folder 4)
    Hawaiian Pineapple Company. Hale, Marion Mason. The Kingdom that Grew Out of a Little Boy's Garden. Honolulu, HI: Hawaiian Pineapple Company, 1929.
  - The Hawaiian Electric Company, Limited, circa 1959 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Hawaiian Electric Co., Ltd. All Star Cosmopolitan Recipes from Hawaii the 50th State. Honolulu, HI: Home Service Department, The Hawaiian Electric Co., Ltd., circa 1959.
  - Hawaiian Pineapple Growers Association; Association of Hawaiian Pineapple Canners, 1923-1926, 1963-1965 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Association of Hawaiian Pineapple Canners. Ninety-Nine Tempting Pineapple Treats. San Francisco, CA: Association of Hawaiian Pineapple Canners, undated.
    Hawaiian Pineapple Canners. Hawaiian Pineapple as 100 Good Cooks Serve It. San Francisco, CA: Hawaiian Pineapple Canners, 1926.
    Pineapple Growers Association. Canned Pineapple's Garden of Salads (Student Booklet). San Francisco, CA: Pineapple Growers Association, circa 1963.
    Pineapple Growers Association. New York World's Fair 1964-1965 Souvenir Recipes. San Francisco, CA: publisher unknown. Reprint. Home Economics Department, Pineapple Growers Association, circa 1964.